{
    "1":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 60997 + (6012 + 6228) : 3",
        "A": "6407",
        "B": "607",
        "C": "507",
        "D": "6507",
        "CORRECT": "6507"
    },
    "2":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 485 ∙ 2 + 485 ∙ 3",
        "A": "2425",
        "B": "2025",
        "C": "425",
        "D": "225",
        "CORRECT": "2425"
    },
    "3":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: (72507 + 56736) : (350 – 347)",
        "A": "43081",
        "B": "4381",
        "C": "46081",
        "D": "53081",
        "CORRECT": "43081"
    },
    "4":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 483042 : 6 ∙ 8 – 8044",
        "A": "646012",
        "B": "36013",
        "C": "636015",
        "D": "636012",
        "CORRECT": "636012"
    },
    "5":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 55440 : 9 – 10460 : 2",
        "A": "830",
        "B": "940",
        "C": "745",
        "D": "930",
        "CORRECT": "930"
    },
    "6":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 3546 – 283 ∙ 4 + 819",
        "A": "3233",
        "B": "333",
        "C": "233",
        "D": "3400",
        "CORRECT": "3233"
    },
    "7":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 82213 ∙ 3 – 12240 : 3",
        "A": "242600",
        "B": "242559",
        "C": "272559",
        "D": "272459",
        "CORRECT": "242559"
    },
    "8":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: (40179 – 15395 : 5) ∙ 4",
        "A": "148000",
        "B": "153500",
        "C": "158400",
        "D": "148400",
        "CORRECT": "148400"
    },
    "9":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 9805 + 14651 : 7",
        "A": "12000",
        "B": "11898",
        "C": "1188",
        "D": "11900",
        "CORRECT": "11898"
    },
    "10":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: (56043 – 13032) : (900 : 100)",
        "A": "5000",
        "B": "4779",
        "C": "4000",
        "D": "3780",
        "CORRECT": "4779"
    },
    "11":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 500 + (600 – 3 ∙ 100) : 10",
        "A": "430",
        "B": "534",
        "C": "600",
        "D": "530",
        "CORRECT": "530"
    },
    "12":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 1,
        "QUESTION": "Найдите значение выражения: 4 ∙ (932 + 17692) : 6",
        "A": "12412",
        "B": "12500",
        "C": "12416",
        "D": "12414",
        "CORRECT": "12416"
    },
    "13":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: 64-х=91:7",
        "A": "х=51",
        "B": "х=40",
        "C": "х=53",
        "D": "х=-51",
        "CORRECT": "х=51"
    },
    "14":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения:  х+49=4528*4",
        "A": "х=18063",
        "B": "х=17063",
        "C": "х=63",
        "D": "х=-63",
        "CORRECT": "х=18063"
    },
    "15":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: х-54=506-102",
        "A": "х=-55",
        "B": "х=37",
        "C": "х=253",
        "D": "х=458",
        "CORRECT": "х=458"
    },
    "16":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: 4 ∙ (932 + 17692) : 6",
        "A": "12416",
        "B": "12416",
        "C": "12416",
        "D": "12416",
        "CORRECT": "12416"
    },
    "17":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: х-120=45-38",
        "A": "х=37",
        "B": "х=-104",
        "C": "х=127",
        "D": "х=130",
        "CORRECT": "х=127"
    },
    "18":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: 703-х=135*5",
        "A": "х=28",
        "B": "х=18",
        "C": "х=-5",
        "D": "х=47",
        "CORRECT": "х=28"
    },
    "19":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: х+76=978+359",
        "A": "х=2043",
        "B": "х=1261",
        "C": "х=-1092",
        "D": "х=301",
        "CORRECT": "х=1261"
    },
    "20":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: 199-х=605:5",
        "A": "х=-54",
        "B": "х=100",
        "C": "х=48",
        "D": "х=78",
        "CORRECT": "х=78"
    },
    "21":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: х-572=350-156",
        "A": "х=-213",
        "B": "х=543",
        "C": "х=766",
        "D": "х=800",
        "CORRECT": "х=766"
    },
    "22":{
        "TYPE_QUESTION": 2,
        "QUESTION": "Решите уравнения: 879-х=87*8",
        "A": "х=183",
        "B": "х=102",
        "C": "х=-13",
        "D": "х=118",
        "CORRECT": "х=183"
    }
}